{
    "id": "43fb865dfd044195a1ac4ad5614c4aa5",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The attendance …………………….. during the second term.",
            "description": "Fall off = diminish",
            "answers": [
                "fell out",
                "fell off",
                "fell in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "374b3c4b5e54422d9fb53f4b69edb367"
        },
        {
            "question": "At last the rioters ……………………….",
            "description": "Fall back = retreat",
            "answers": [
                "fell back",
                "fell out",
                "fell over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "221340b0d7cb44a68fc1bc7298b2a574"
        },
        {
            "question": "The project ……………………….. for want of financial support.",
            "description": "Fall through = fail",
            "answers": [
                "fell through",
                "fell out",
                "fell back"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f720c3a2cd9c4f728198033b371529b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The dog ……………………….. me without any provocation.",
            "description": "Get at = attack",
            "answers": [
                "got on",
                "got at",
                "got off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3514940d7343421985b08ab868134c3e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The chief guest ………………………….. the prizes.",
            "description": "Give away = distribute",
            "answers": [
                "gave up",
                "gave off",
                "gave away"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bea3c4e3de5549c28c79b9a9341d51ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has ………………………… too much in her life.",
            "description": "Go through = suffer",
            "answers": [
                "gone over",
                "gone through",
                "gone after"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "36ef19f1362b468ca1e6617fdc171f94"
        },
        {
            "question": "The travelers were ……………………….. by the robbers.",
            "description": "Hold up = to stop on the highway and rob",
            "answers": [
                "held off",
                "held up",
                "held over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c7417161498b4276b6d1d6fd0e24f36d"
        },
        {
            "question": "One must try to ………………………. the reputation of one’s family.",
            "description": "Keep up = maintain",
            "answers": [
                "keep up",
                "keep on",
                "keep in"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1d9e1cb8be494f2cba2edd305419350c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Since the offender was a minor, he was ……………………….. with a fine.",
            "description": "To let somebody off is to punish them leniently.",
            "answers": [
                "let up",
                "let over",
                "let off"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "30dfca40353d418294b501ea91ee0166"
        },
        {
            "question": "Things are ……………………….. for us.",
            "description": "Look up can mean improve.",
            "answers": [
                "looking over",
                "looking up",
                "looking on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3431dc43a9934615a99893d0213871ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t hear that. It completely ………………………….",
            "description": "When something passes you by, you fail to notice it.",
            "answers": [
                "passed me over",
                "passed me up",
                "passed me by"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9e81a0e5e0684a3781fbc3aebc425b1f"
        },
        {
            "question": "Before he even realized it, life just …………………………..",
            "description": "When something passes you by, you fail to notice it or take advantage of it.",
            "answers": [
                "passed him by",
                "passed him off",
                "passed him over"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "df0f394f1fac4d33b3690e96856c79cc"
        }
    ]
}